情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day.
Oh, happy Valentine's Day.
那今晚去弗里特利餐馆咯
So, Fratelli's tonight?
我来了 奶油糕饼
Hello, cannoli canoe.
我喜欢 很合身
I like it. Nice fit.
面料时髦
Swanky material.
杰 你看起来又壮又性感
Jay, you look so strong and sexy.
像个奥运会摔跤健将 同时又是个款爷
Like an Olympic wrestler, but with money.
-到你的了 -好的
- Your turn. - Okay.
情人节是我最喜欢的美国节日
This is my favorite day in America.
情人节快乐 美女
Happy Valentine's Day, gorgeous.
好大啊
They're huge!
-我的天啊 -是啊 肯定好看
- Oh, my God. - Yeah, those will work.
-真漂亮 -你今晚戴着吧
- Beautiful. - You can wear 'em tonight.
我准备了惊喜
I have a surprise.
莫非你终于要带我去跳莎莎舞吗
Don't tell me you're finally taking me salsa dancing!
大卫·布伦纳是谁
And who's David Brenner?
拉斯维加斯的传奇人物
Only a Vegas legend.
他是魔术师吗 我可喜欢魔术师了
Is he a magician? 'Cause I love magicians.
他是个喜剧大师
He's a comedian.
喜剧大师 可今天是情人节啊
A comedian? It's Valentine's Day.
我还以为是去跳莎莎舞呢 别去看喜剧嘛
I thought we were going salsa dancing, not to watch a comedian.
你会爱死他的 相信我
You're gonna love him. Trust me.
那家伙可逗了
The guy's hilarious.
好吧 说一个他的段子
Okay, tell me one of his jokes.
他可不说段子
He doesn't do jokes.
-那他有小木槌吗 -没
- Does he have a mallet? -No.
那他怎么打头逗笑啊
So then how does he get hit in the head?
他不需要打头逗笑
He doesn't get hit in the head.
他观察在场的观众们
He- He makes observations.
然后用幽默的方式说出来
He tells the truth in a funny way.
拜托 他上过无数次《鲁豫有约》了
Come on. He's been on Johnny Carson a hundred times.
鲁豫又是谁
Who the hell is Johnny Carson?
老天爷啊
Oh, for God's sake.
我和歌洛莉亚不是一辈人
Gloria and I are from different generations.
老实说 我很难跟她交流
And I won't lie- It isn't always easy.
上个星期 她还以为
I mean, last week she thought
"西蒙和加韦科"组合是我的律师呢
Simon and Garfunkel were my lawyers.
我可没
No I didn't.
我开玩笑的呢
It was a joke.
我没听懂笑点
I don't get it.
可能是因为我没小木槌逗你笑
Maybe that's because there's no mallet.
是啊 我现在就想用木槌捶死你
Yeah, I wish I had a mallet right now.
...打算待在加州北部
...was to stay in Northern California.
你有没告诉她 需要多长时间
Did you indicate to her how long that you were gonna take?
-情人节快乐 -情人节快乐
- Happy Valentine's Day. - Happy Valentine's Day.
-情人节快乐 爹地 -情人节快乐 莉莉
- Happy Valentine's Day, Daddy. - Happy Valentine's Day, Lily.
发现什么特别的了吗
Notice anything different?
-真有爱 -有爱而已吗
- Oh, that is cute. - Cute?
我们花了很长时间打扮呢
We spent a lot of time on this.
我可没看出来
I don't see how.
你只是拆了一条羽毛围巾而已
You just cut up one of your boas.
其实 我们重新改造了一下
Uh- Actually, no. We repurposed it.
我们走的是名人混搭风
It was sort of a Bob Mackie meets Martha Stewart project.
好吧 我们还以为能给你个惊喜呢
Okay. Well, we just thought it would be a nice surprise.
其实没什么好惊喜的
It's hardly a surprise. I mean,
逢年过节你都会把她打扮一番
you dress her up for every holiday.
我昨晚给她洗澡时
I was giving her a bath last night,
我发现马丁·路德·金的妆还在呢
and I still saw traces of Martin Luther King behind her ear.
好吧 你不喜欢 我们懂了
All right. Not in the spirit. We get it.
不不 对不起
No, I'm-I'm sorry.
不 你弄得很好看 只是我
No. It's adorable. I just-
我真的很担心我的结案陈词
I'm really nervous about my closing argument.
你都练了好几个星期了
Oh, you've been rehearsing for weeks.
你会发挥出色的
You're gonna be great.
但愿如此吧
Let's hope so.
对了 我在想
Hey, and I was wondering-
既然你一整天都要在法院里
since you're gonna be in court all day-
你想吃巧克力就先吃吧
You can open the chocolates.
好极了
Score.
你好 迪兰
Hi, Dylan.
邓菲太太 情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day, Mrs. Dunphy.
迪兰 谢谢啊 你真贴心
Oh. Dylan, thank you. That is so sweet.
要是所有老女人都像你这样有气质就好了
You know, all women should look as tasty as you when they're old.
这话听着怪怪的
Huh. Conflicted.
嘿 宝贝儿
Hey, baby.
这份礼物代表了我对你的钟情
Hey. Take this sweet gift as a token of my affection,
对你的爱慕和无尽的爱意
my unending love and admiration-
我的天 真大啊
Oh, my God. Yay, it's big!
天呐
Oh, my God.
爱死了 这是我见过最漂亮的东西
I love it. It's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
你得用紫外灯照着看看[精液斑斑]
Seriously, you gotta put a black light on it.
会美得让你犯晕呢
It'll blow your mind.
迪兰 原来你还会画画啊
Wow! Dylan, I didn't know you could paint.
不不 我只是照了张照片
Oh, I didn't. I just took a photo
然后用软件处理了一下
and I put it through this program
就把它变成画了
that turns it into a painting.
所以你们还真的做过
So you two actually did...
-那个 -嗯嗯
- that. - Uh-huh.
是啊
Yeah.
我们把它挂在我床头吧
Let's go put this over my bed.
不行 不行
Not- No, no.
那东西不能进你闺房
You don't need to be in the bedroom at all.
我替你保管
I'll take it.
他比我浪漫吗 迪迪仔
Did he trump me? D-Money.
你说呢 他把一张照片做成了一幅画
You tell me. He made a painting out of a photograph one time.
而我只是送一张贺卡
I have hand-picked a card,
偷偷在浴室的镜子上画一颗心
drawn a heart in the steam on the medicine cabinet,
然后带克莱尔去弗里特利餐厅
and taken Claire to Fratelli's,
去吃意大利家常菜
a family-style Italian restaurant,
17年来一成不变
for 17 years in a row.
毫无疑问 他比我浪漫多了
Yeah, he got me. He got me.
-再见 宝贝 -待会儿见
- Bye, honey. - See you later.
待会儿见
See you later.
菲尔 你这是闹哪出
Phil, what is that?
我们今晚也不是非要去弗里特利餐厅啦
You know, we don't have to go to Fratelli's tonight.
好啊 那你有什么好主意
Okay, what do you have in mind?
我嘛 觉得你可以去酒店开房爽一晚
Well, I thought you might enjoy a night at a hotel.
好啊 不过你在家带孩子行吗
I would, but would you and the kids be okay?
-我也和你去啊 -好的 我懂了
- I meant together. - Yes, I know.
我当然懂 明白了
Oh. I know. I know. I got it.
那 你意下如何
So, what do you think?
我想你今晚就别想睡了
I think you're not getting any sleep tonight,
所以你今天上班时好好歇着吧
so you might want to take a nap at work today.
我一向如此
I always do.
菲尔 亲爱的
Phil? Sweetie.
既然我们要玩点儿情色的
As long as we're talking about being a little bit naughty,
你觉得来点儿角色扮演怎样
what would you say to a little role-playing?
-角色扮演啊 -嗯嗯
- Role-play? - Mm-hmm.
好啊
I'm in.
我去安排孩子们今晚住别人家
I'll set up sleepovers for the kids.
那我下班后来接你吧
And I'll swing by after work to pick you up.
不不 要不你到酒店的酒吧去找我呗
No, no. Why don't you meet me in the hotel bar
看看你能不能在哪儿钓到我
and see if you can pick me up there.
小心点 小姐 你会唤醒一头沉睡的"雄"狮哦
Careful, lady. You're gonna wake up a sexy sleeping giant.
也许我可以扮演雷金纳德·阿普比
Perhaps I'll be Reginald Appleby,
一位来参加马球比赛的英国绅士
an English gentleman in town for a polo match.
菲尔
Phil.
要不 一位来自香港的优雅商人
Or...Honorable businessman from Hong Kong.
再说就性趣全无了
Kinda wrecking it.
没什么大不了的 克莱尔
It's not a big deal, Claire.
我只是个拿皮鞭的驯兽师
I just train tigers for a living.
太重口味了吗
Too... No?
这些是玫瑰花瓣吗
Are these rose petals?
是的 为了纪念我们的爱情
Yes, to commemorate our love.
我被迫和解[安定下来]
I had to settle.
你妈或许会认为你是"被迫"的
Well, your mom might think so,
不过其他人都觉得我是个贤夫哦
but a lot of people think I'm a catch.
不 我是说那案子 我差点儿就要成功了
No. The case. I- I was this close to nailing it,
可我的委托人临阵退缩 和解了
and then my client gets scared and settles.
真遗憾 来颗巧克力吧
I'm sorry. Maybe you'd like a chocolate.
我可是一颗也没偷吃哦
Notice that I have not eaten any of the chocolates.
盒子原本有两层的 你我心里都清楚
There were two levels. You know it and I know it.
真是太受打击了
This is so frustrating.
我精心准备了有史以来最强的结案陈词
I had one of the greatest closing arguments of all time-
控诉"大政府"如何欺压"小人民"
all about the big government rolling over the little guy,
而且我还想好了如何推向高潮
and I even had this great moment at the end...
我会指着国徽高呼 "可耻啊"
where I would point to the state seal and I'd say, "Shame!"
原来你洗澡时是在练这个啊
Oh, that's what you were doing in the shower.
我那时还担心呢
I was a little worried.
是曼尼来了
Um, that's Manny.
我答应今晚照看他 希望你别介意
I said we would watch him tonight. I hope you don't mind.
我没想到你今天会这么倒霉
I didn't know you were gonna be going through all this.
没关系 有个孩子在挺好的
No, it's fine. It might be nice to have him around.
他总是能逗我发笑
He always make me laugh.
嗨 曼尼
Hi, Manny.
世界又冷酷又无情
The universe is cold and loveless.
怎么了 情人节过得不好吗
Uh-oh. Bad Valentine's Day?
我追寻我的爱人 菲奥娜·冈德森
I went for the gold- Fiona Gunderson.
我倾心吐胆地为她写了首诗 放在她桌子上
I poured my heart and soul into a poem, left it on her desk.
我甚至把纸边烧了一下 让它更好看些
I even burned the edges to make it look fancy.
她不喜欢吗
And she didn't like it?
她很喜欢
Oh, she loved it.
可有个叫德卡斯的小崽子说是他写的
But this kid Durkas told her he wrote it.
曼尼 那你为什么不告诉她真相呢
Well, Manny, why-why didn't you just tell her the truth?
她那时已经走了
She was already gone.
而且他俩要去我最喜欢的餐厅约会
And she's on a date with him at my favorite restaurant,
美奶昔餐厅
Great Shakes.
你怎么知道啊
How do you know all this?
我在信里邀请她去那儿的
I invited her in the poem.
就在那诗句之后
Right after the line of,
"五大湖水深千尺 不及我爱你之情"
"My love is deeper than the Great Lakes."
好吧 这简直无法容忍
Okay, well, this is unacceptable.
我的天 又来了
Oh, boy. Here we go.
不 其实没什么难的
No, it's not that big of a deal.
接下来我们这么干
This is what we're gonna do.
我们去美奶昔餐厅 找张桌子坐下
We're gonna shoot over to Great Shakes, get a table.
曼尼去追回他的挚爱
Manny can reclaim the love of his life.
你我去弄点好吃的
You and I can get a couple Mudslides.
我觉得不太好
I don't know.
德卡斯也在那儿
Durkas is gonna be there.
那小崽子可壮了
I've seen the kid do a pull-up.
曼尼 今天是情人节
Hey, Manny, it's Valentine's Day.
今天不是逃离爱情的日子
It's not the day you run away from love.
而是追逐爱情 收获爱情的日子
It's the day you track it down, tie it up and take it home.
要是我们能成功
Now, if we can pull this off,
你和你的小女朋友就能倚在吧台前
you and your little lady friend will be belly up to a ice cream counter
浪漫地共享一杯奶昔
having a milk shake with two straws.
你看如何
What do you say?
我喜欢
I like it.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
科学家也无法解释这个现象
Scientists- They don't know why this is true,
可确实如此
but it's true.
大屁股的女人能长寿
Women with big rear ends live longer.
但夸女人屁股大的男人会短命
Man who tell 'em that don't.
你们听过这么件事没有
Did you read about this man,
有个91岁的老头在德州抢银行
a 91 -year old bank robber in Texas?
他走进银行
He goes into a bank-
"我要干什么来着"
"The hell did I want?"
他们照下了四千张他逃离银行的照片
They had over 4,000 photos of him escaping from the bank.
是吧 他很逗 对吧
See? He's funny, huh?
能坐你旁边吗
Mind if I join you?
我叫克里夫 克里夫·比克斯比
I'm Clive. Clive Bixby.
我看到了 我叫朱莉安娜
Yes, I can see that. I'm Juliana.
克里夫 你是来这儿开会的
So, Clive, you in town for a convention,
还是只是老记不住自己的名字
or do you just forget your name a lot?
性感小野猫爪子挺锋利嘛
Pretty kitty has nails.
我喜欢
I like that.
我是来参加交易会的
I'm in town for a trade show.
我设计高级电声转换器
I design high-end electroacoustic transducers.
那可真是
Wow, that is very...
特别啊
specific.
意思是我能让东西叫出声
It's a fancy way of saying I get things to make noise.
那你呢
So, what's your story?
你是选美佳丽吗
Miss America Pageant in town?
你跟女人搭讪很顺溜啊 克里夫
You're a pretty smooth talker, Clive.
我全身上下都很"顺溜"
I'm pretty smooth all over.
先生 本餐厅禁止吸烟
Sir, there's no smoking in here.
好的 其实我也不抽烟
Oh, that's fine. I'm not actually a smoker.
你真像个小童子军 克里夫
You're quite the Boy Scout, Clive.
我问你 今晚你有没兴趣
Tell me, would you be interested in
来赢一枚小勋章呢
earning a merit badge tonight?
你会捆绑 会打结吗
Do you know anything about tying knots?
我或许不该找你聊天的
I probably shouldn't be talking to you.
我是有妇之夫
I'm a married man.
正好 我就喜欢有妇之夫
Well, I just so happen to like married men.
跟我说说你妻子吧
Tell me about your wife.
她非常漂亮 必须的
Well, she's beautiful, of course.
是吗 既然她那么漂亮
Really? Well, if she's so very beautiful,
你怎么会跟我在一起呢
why are you here with me?
因为她总是很疲惫
Because she's always so tired...
而且她总是忙着使唤我干活儿
and she's always making lists of things for me to do.
也许如果你听她使唤 她就不会这么累了
Maybe if you did them she wouldn't be so tired.
不 她吩咐的事根本做不完
Oh no. She can make list for days.
不过说回你的性感双唇
But back to your mouth and how sexy it is.
不不 我倒是想说回那些"使唤"
Mm-mmm. I wanna go back to these alleged lists
还有你那唠叨的妻子
and your nagging wife.
我不是在说你
I'm not talking about you.
我不是那个意思 再重来一次好吗
I didn't mean that. Can we try this again?
好吧
Yeah.
那既然你妻子这么漂亮
So if your wife is so beautiful,
你怎么会跟我在一起呢
why are you here with me?
因为
Because...
我太疼她了
I respect her too much...
所以我不忍对她下手
to do to her...
像对你般地蹂躏她
what I'm going to do to you?
噢 中大奖了
Oh, jackpot.
我一会儿就回来 克里夫
I'll be right back, Clive.
你发现她了吗 她在这儿吗
Do you have eyes on her? Is she here?
两点钟方向 坐在后排桌子的金发女生
Two o'clock- blonde at the back table.
明白 发现目标了
Yep. I have a visual.
别再用这种军事用语了 完毕
Let's not talk like that anymore. Over.
好 就这么干 我要去赢回我的爱人
Okay, this is it. I'm off to win the heart of my beloved.
这真是件好事
Well, this is nice.
如果没法好好过自己的情人节
I mean, if we can't have our own Valentine's Day,
能帮别人过个好节也不错
it's nice that we can give somebody else one.
好吧 小卡 对不起
All right, Cam. I'm sorry.
我很抱歉 忽视了你的精心安排
I'm sor- I'm sorry I have not been attentive.
过去五个月来
I've been spending the last five months...
我呕心沥血
pouring my core beliefs
写出了自己最棒的讲稿
into the greatest speech that I will ever write,
但一切努力却付诸东流
and then that moment gets taken away.
老弟 情况如何
Hey, buddy. How'd it go?
我做不来 德卡斯在那儿呢
I can't do it, not while Durkas is there.
他有种天生的自信 我对他又敬又怕
He has the natural confidence. I admire it and fear it.
我们会搞定他的 我们得计划一下
We will deal with him directly. We need a plan.
你敢再戏剧化一点吗
Could you be more dramatic?
我们得计划一下
We need a plan.
在俄勒冈州
In Oregon,
立法会颁布了一项法令
the state legislature ratified a, uh, bill...
规定从今往后
that from now on
人和动物发生性关系将被视为犯罪
it is a crime to have sex in Oregon with a farm animal.
俄勒冈的女人是有多丑啊
How ugly are the women in Oregon?
杰 他太逗了
He's funny, Jay.
对啊 没说错吧
I know. See?
-我看得出来 你肯定不是从俄勒冈来的 -不是
- I can tell you're not- you're not from Oregon. -No.
-你美极了 -谢谢
- You are gorgeous. - Thank you.
谢谢你带你爸爸来看我表演
Thank you for bringing your father to the show.
不对 我是她丈夫 大卫
Oh, no. I'm her husband, Dave.
-没开玩笑吧 -没呢
- No kidding. - Yeah.
和他结婚的感觉如何啊
What's it like to be married to someone
那家伙估计和《圣经》一样老了吧
who was there when the Bible was written?
你们那时候叫什么 就叫《箴言录》吗
What was it called then? Just "The Testament"?
真是 真是有意思
That's, uh- That's- That's good stuff.
现在他就想关灯睡觉了
Oh, now he's trying to turn out the light.
有电话找您 在那边
Phone call. Over there.
-喂 -喂 您好
- Hello? - Uh, yes. Hello.
-是德卡斯先生吗 -是我
- Mr. Durkas? - Yeah.
我是唐·卓立
This is Don Jolly...
我是"美奶昔"公司的
with the Great Shakes corporate office,
我有个好消息告诉您
and I have good news for you.
您被抽中参与我们的调查
You have been selected to take part in a random survey...
而且您将获得现金奖励
that you could win cash and prizes.
您有兴趣参加我们的活动吗
Does that sound like something you'd be interested in?
好啊 当然
Yeah, sure.
好的 我们只是问您几个小问题
Okay, just a few simple questions for you.
您能否根据自己的喜好
Would you please rank your favorite ice creams
把美奶昔的冰激凌排一下序
at Great Shakes from least favorite to favorite?
我其实也不太熟悉产品
I don't know 'em by heart.
您右手边应该就有一本菜单
There should be a menu right there to your right.
在你右边 好了 开始吧
To your right. Mm-hmm. There you go.
你好 曼尼
Oh. Hi, Manny.
你好 菲奥娜 我能坐下吗
Hi, Fiona. Can I join you?
-可以吧 -谢谢
- I guess so. -Thanks.
你不必担心他会出轨 那是肯定的
And you don't have to worry about him cheating. That's for sure.
如果他出轨了 你肯定会发现的
Because if he does, you'll catch him...
因为他回家时嘴里肯定有两副假牙
when he comes home with two sets of teeth in his mouth.
是啊
Yeah.
给我们说说 他在新婚之夜表现如何
So tell me, on the wedding night, what-what did he do?
他是不是说想换个舒服的做爱姿势
Did he say he wanted to change into something comfortable
然后就一睡不起了
and go into a coma?
-我想去去洗手间 -别去嘛
- Listen, I gotta use the men's room. - Nuh-uh.
我必须去一趟 马上就回来
I gotta use the men's room. I'll be right back.
你要去哪儿 等会儿
Where you going? Wait a minute.
我只是开玩笑的 我就是干这个的
I'm only joking. That's what I do.
你比我可年轻多了
You know, you're way younger than I am.
你只是看着显老
You just don't look it.
克里夫 我有点儿小东西给你
Clive, I have a little something for you.
是什么
What is it?
我的裙子
My dress.
-我的胸罩 -我的天
- My bra. - Oh, my g-
我的小内内
My underwear.
-我的天 -嗯嗯
- My God. - Yeah.
要不我们拿着这些上楼去吧
What do you say we take this upstairs?
这比吃意大利菜好太多了
This is so much better than cheesy garlic bread.
-巧克力味 -好的 继续
- Chocolate. - Uh-huh. Go on.
-香草味 -我正记着呢
- Vanilla. - I'm taking copious notes.
您继续说 德卡斯先生
Keep goin', Mr. Durkas.
如果诗不是泰德写的 他为什么骗人呢
So, why would Ted say he wrote the poem if he didn't?
也许是因为你是校花
Maybe because you're the cutest girl in school,
而且你回眸一笑就倾国倾城
and you have a laugh that makes science lab seem like recess.
那你愿不愿意
Would you be more or less inclined
去"美奶昔"公司做客
to visit a Great Shakes establishment...
如果你事先知道你的愿望都会被满足
if you knew your satisfaction was guaranteed?
-真是个傻逼问题 -不好意思
- That's a dumb question. - Excuse me.
我这问题不傻逼 先生
It is not a dumb question, Mr. -
-该死 他挂了 -那你不必装那口音了
- Tarnation! He hung up. - Then you can drop the accent.
迪尔加多 你在这儿干嘛
Delgado. What are you doing here?
在讨论诗歌呢 你想背诵一下你的作品吗
Discussing poetry. Maybe you'll like to recite some of yours.
我才不背什么东西呢
I'm not gonna recite anything.
承认吧 那首诗根本不是你写的
Just admit you didn't write the poem.
我不知道他在说什么
I don't know what he's talking about.
赶紧滚蛋 别逼我揍你一顿
Get out of here before you get your butt kicked.
-我要过去一下 -不 我来吧
- I'm going over there. - No, I got this.
喂 喂 先生 先生 转回去
Whoa! Whoa, sir! Sir? Turn around.
先生 你无权
Sir, you have no right
把他人的作品据为己有
to claim ownership of another person's work.
你算老几
Who are you?
我是个律师
I'm a lawyer.
你还有律师啊
You have a lawyer?
你说谎是一回事
It is one thing to lie,
但你竟然接着又欺负这位年轻人 简直不可饶恕
but then to bully this young man- it's unforgivable.
这就是当今世界的不公平
And this is what's wrong with the world today.
大块头
The big guy...
自以为能凌驾于小家伙之上
thinks that he can roll right over the little guy...
直到小家伙说"够了"
until the little guy says, "Enough."
而那正是这位小家伙要做的
And that's what this little guy's doing-
就在此时 此刻
right here, right now.
能别再叫我"小家伙"了吗 我还不算矮的呢
Can we stop calling me "Little guy"? I'm in the 40th percentile.
嘘 看我的吧
Shh. I got this.
泰德·德卡斯 显然没有写那首诗
Ted Durkas clearly did not write that poem.
我清楚 他心里也清楚
I know it. He knows it.
你好好问问自己 菲奥娜
Deep down in your heart, Fiona-
你一定也清楚
You know it too.
可耻啊
Shame!
好吧 随便了 我是偷了他的傻逼诗
Fine! Whatever. I stole his stupid poem.
-你偷的 -我就说嘛
- You did? - I told you.
认罪吧
There you go.
我这么做 是因为我有此深情
I only did it because I had the feelings,
我只是不知道如何向你表达
I just didn't know how to show 'em.
真的吗 从来没人对我做如此甜蜜的事
Really? That's the sweetest thing anyone's ever done for me.
开什么玩笑啊
You've gotta be kidding me.
-走吧 这妞儿是个二逼青年 -绝对的
- Let's get out of here. This chick's crazy. - Seriously.
我从没见过你如此霸气啊
I've never seen you like that.
你无法想象那种感觉有多爽
You have no idea how good that felt.
情人节快乐 律师先生
Well, happy Valentine's Day, counselor.
我们发展得真快啊 朱莉安娜
This is all happening so fast, Juliana.
是啊 而且我午夜之前必须赶回家陪老公
I know, and I have to be home to my husband by midnight.
哟 纠结的剧情
Ooh, a twist.
菲尔 菲尔 我的外套卡住了
Phil! Phil, my coat is stuck.
-菲尔是谁 -不 别闹了 认真点儿
- Who's Phil? - No, not now! Seriously.
-我的外套卡住了 -宝贝 快把外套脱掉
- My coat is stuck. - Oh, oh. Honey, take off your coat!
-开什么玩笑啊 快拔 -我的天啊
- Are you kidding me? Pull it. - Oh, my goodness.
快拔 用力 用力
Pull it. Come on. Come on.
天呐 这回完了 这回完了
Oh, boy. Not good. Not good.
好了 好了 好了
Okay. Okay. Okay.
快上来吧 就当是爬楼梯了
Come on up. Treat 'em like they're regular stairs.
-没事了 -快过去吧
- It's okay. - Come on through.
情人节快乐 您真美
Happy Valentine's Day. You look lovely.
-您也美 我没别的意思 -我懂
- So do you. Not in a weird way. - Yeah.
-你好 嗨 -嗨
- How are you? Hi. - Hi.
-情人节快乐 -让我来弄弄
- Happy Valentine's- - Let me just get in here.
让我来弄弄
Let me get in here.
-好的 -菲尔
- Okay? - Phil?
-嘿 汤姆 -嘿
- Hey, Tom. - Hi.
你好啊 亲爱的
How are you? Honey
克莱尔 还记得我同事汤姆·麦克森吗
Claire, you remember Tom Mickleson from the office
-还有他妻子 苏珊 -记得 你们好
- and his wife, Susan. - I do. Hey.
你的外套卡住了吗
Is your coat stuck?
是啊 卡得死死的了
It is. It really is. It's in there pretty darn good.
何不脱下来呢
Why don't you take it off?
我...觉得很冷
Um, I'm freezing cold.
来吧 让我试试
At least let me give it a shot.
-不必了吧 -没事没事 看我的
- Oh, I don't think... - No, no, no. I got it.
-邓菲先生 夫人 -嗨
- Mr. And Mrs. Dunphy? - Hey.
-巴拉班校长 -你好啊
- Principal Balaban. - Hey, how are you?
克里夫·比克斯比是谁啊
Who's Clive Bixby?
他是个推销扩音器的
Oh, uh, he makes speakers.
-他是来参加交易会的 -菲尔
- He's actually in town for a trade show. - Phil.
天 你被卡住了吗
My, are you stuck?
是啊 有点儿
Yeah, I am. A little bit.
何不把外套脱了呢
Why don't you take off that coat?
我怕冷
Um, I'm chilly.
真是卡死在这儿了
It's really jammed in here.
-让我过去试试 我帮你 -不必了 我们没事
- Let me in there. I'll get you. - No, I think we're okay.
邓菲太太
Mrs. Dunphy?
开什么玩笑啊
Are you kidding me?
嗨 这位是卢克的数学老师 帕斯沃小姐
Hi! Luke's math teacher, Ms. Passwater.
"拍死我"
"Passwater."
老杰 别在意他说的
Ah, Jay, papi, don't pay attention to what he's saying.
他只是开玩笑的
He's just being funny.
但他说的是事实
Because he points out the truth.
观众们笑是因为他们也觉得确实如此
Those people were laughing because they saw it too.
-你干嘛在意他们怎么想 -我不在意
- What do you care what they think? - I don't.
我在意你怎么想
I care what you think.
我爱你 你是我的爱人
I love you. You're my valentine.
只是现在而已
Yeah, for now.
等我80岁了呢
But what about when I'm 80
我坐在轮椅上 插着氧气管
and I'm in a wheelchair, on oxygen?
你还会要我吗
You still gonna want me?
你以为我如此肤浅吗
Do you think I'm so shallow
你老了我就会抛弃你吗
that I'm gonna leave you when you're old?
如果我胖了100磅 你会抛弃我吗
What if I gain a hundred pounds? You gonna leave me then?
-不会 -你怎么犹豫了一下
- No. - What's with the pause?
你这假设不公平啊
Well, it's not exactly fair.
我变老是必然的 可你不一定会变胖
I mean, I have to get old. You don't have to get fat.
要是我想变胖 就能变胖
If I want to get fat, I get fat.
那好 如果你胖了
Okay, fine. And if you do,
我也会守着你 不信你试试
I'll be there. You'll see.
是啊 你看我怎么变胖
Yeah, watch me. Watch me, how I get fat.
-我能变胖的 -那我也会守着你
- I can get fat. - And I'll be there.
很好
Good.
-你还想回去看戏吗 -不去了
- You wanna go back in? - No.
我有个更好的主意
I got a better idea.
我们去跳莎莎舞吧 那家伙也不怎么有趣
Let's go salsa dancing. This guy's not that funny.
好极了
Perfect.
好了 好了 我打给维修部了
We're good! We're good! I talked to Maintenance.
他们 他们马上就来 大家忙去吧
They're- They're- They're coming, so go on ahead.
再见 回头见吧
See you guys. See you later.
学校里见 见到你们真开心
See you in school. Good to see you guys.
维修部的人会解决的
Maintenance is gonna take care of it.
-我们得救了 -好吧 好吧 他们要多久才到
- So we're fine. - Okay. Okay, how long till they get here?
我是骗他们的 没人来救我们
I was faking it. No one's coming for us.
那就去找人啊 快点儿
Well, then, go and get them! Hurry!
此刻是我这辈子最糗的时刻
That was the most embarrassing moment of my life.
克莱尔 菲尔
Claire! Phil!
淡定
Stand by.
怎么了 腰带卡住了吗
What, did you get your belt stuck?
是啊 卡住了
I did. Yeah.
那把外套脱了呗 我帮你吧
Take your coat off. Here, let me help you.
-别别 老爸 我没事 -得了吧
- No, no, Dad. Dad, I'm fine. - Come on!
莫非你里面没穿衣服吗
What are you, naked under there?
-我靠 -没关系
- Aw, geez. - It's okay.
-让我来吧 -好吧
- I got this. - Okay.
-克莱尔 照我说的办 -好的
- Claire, follow my lead. - Okay.
好吧
Okay.
-哇塞 -好了
- Wow. - Okay.
-谢谢 -我以前也有同样的经历
- Thank you. - It has happened to me before.
她真有一手啊
That was impressive.
克里夫 下次玩点正常的吧
Take it down a notch, Clive.
-你还好吧 -嗯 挺好
- You okay? - Yeah. I'm good.
-好吧 -我没事
- All right. - I'm good.
-情人节快乐 -情人节快乐
- Happy Valentine's Day. - Happy Valentine's Day.
-再见 -再见
- Chao. - Okay. See ya.
再见 晚安
Bye. Good night.
哎呀妈呀
Oh. That's-
不好意思 再见吧
Sorry. See you, guys.
喂 宝贝
Hi, honey.
嗨 我就是想告诉你 你昨晚真棒
Hey, I just wanted to tell you how great you were last night.
-菲尔 -对不起 我把油弄得到处都是
- Uh, Phil... - Sorry I got the, uh- the oil everywhere, but, hey"
-亲爱的 -幸好不是自家的床单
- Uh, sweetie. - They're not our sheets, right?
宝贝 还记得卖车的人怎么说的吗
Honey- Honey, remember when the salesman told us...
他说"丰田塞纳是适合全家人的车"
that the Sienna was built with the whole family in mind?
全家人都听见你刚刚说的话了
Yeah. Well, the whole family just heard that.
囧 看来
Uh- Uh- Guess-
看来蓝牙对讲挺好用的嘛
I guess the Bluetooth works.
-嗯嗯 -你们用油干嘛
- Mmm. - Why did you have oil?
因为啊 小弟 我们在做炸薯条啊
Because, buddy, we were making French fries.
在你卧室里炸啊
In your room?
要不你们播张DVD看吧
Why don't you guys just pop in a DVD?